

KARMOH SHERIFF

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

DETAILS

Address

Hvidovrevej 180 2650, Hvidovre Denmark

Phone

53 85 05 70

Email

karmoh.sheriff@gmail.com

Birthdate / Place

16/08/1995 Oslo, Norway

Nationality

Norwegian

EDUCATION

Graphic Design Specialization AAS

Houston Community College Sep 2016 – May 2020

COMPETENCES

Adobe: Photoshop • Illustrator • InDesign • Lightroom • Premiere

Pro • After Effects

Microsoft: Word • PowerPoint •

Excel • Outlook

Experience With: HTML • CSS •

Final Cut Pro

LANGUAGES

Norwegian – First Language English – Fluent

Danish - Intermediate

PROFILE

Graphic designer with experience working on various projects, ranging from package design to social media content. I also have experience with photography, videography, and web design. I am coachable and passionate about collaborating with a team when working on projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Multimedia Designer - Freelance

Houston Texas, USA | Aug 2016 - Nov 2022

- Design various marketing and advertisement materials for local businesses.
- Capture and edit product and portrait photos.
- Produce and edit videos for local clients.
- Plan and communicate project details with clients.
- Develop project briefs based on the client's preferences, needs and budget.

Production Assistant - Right Time Solutions

Houston Texas, USA | Feb 2021 - Nov 2022

- Produce videos for corporate, weddings, and a variety of events.
- Capture and edit product photos for local clients.
- Manage and operate studio equipment.
- Manage Social media page for the studio.

Junior Graphic Designer - Inkflo Print & Design Solutions

Houston Texas, USA | Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

- Prepare files for print and ensure appropriate settings and materials are used.
- Manage print queue and production to meet project deadlines.
- Design marketing materials, signage, and packaging to customer specifications.
- Operate printers and software with correct settings.
- Add finishing touches to completed print jobs.